{"Question":"Solve the inequality: x+7 < 12","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":1,"Answer":"x < 5","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[x+7, < , 12, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Solve the inequality: y+3 < 15","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":1,"Answer":null,"Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[y+3, <, 15, y, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Inequality: -2y>=14","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":1,"Answer":null,"Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[-2*y, >= , 14, y, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Inequality:-4x +3  <=5","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":null,"Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[-4*x+3 , <=, 5, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Solve: -11y + 4 > 15","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":null,"Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[-11*y + 4, > , 15, y, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Solve: (b/3) <= 4","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":"b<=12","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[b/3, <= , 4, b, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Solve the inequality: 3(4x-5) > -6","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":"x>3/4","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[3*(4*x-5), >, -6,x, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Solve the inequality: 5x+4 >= 7x + 16","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":"x<=-6","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[5*x+4, >=, 7*x + 16, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Solve: -x-5 <3x-11","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":null,"Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[-x-5, <, 3*x-11, x , solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"What numbers satisfy the condition: twice a number plus one is greater than negative three?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":"x > -2","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[2*x + 1, > , -3, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"What numbers satisfy the condition: eight more than three times a number is less than or equal to fourteen?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":"x <= 2","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[3*x + 8, <= , 14, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"What numbers satisfy the condition: nine less than negative four times a number is strictly greater than negative one?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":"x < -2","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[-4*x - 9, > , -1, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"If five is added to three times a number, then the result is less than twenty.","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":"x < 5","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[3*x + 5, < , 20, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"The sum of three times a number and  4 is greater than negative  8","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":2,"Answer":"x > -4 ","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[3*x + 4, > , -8, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Arleen got a $20 gift card for the coffee shop. Her favorite iced drink costs $3.79. What is the maximum number of drinks she can buy with the gift card?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":3,"Answer":"x<=5","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[3.79*d, <= , 20 , d , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A water taxi has a maximum load of 1,800 pounds. If the average weight of one person is 150 pounds, how many people can safely ride in the water taxi?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":3,"Answer":"x<=12","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[150*p, <= , 1800 , p , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Ryan charges his neighbors $17.50 to wash their car. How many cars must he wash next summer if his goal is to earn at least $1,500?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":3,"Answer":"x>=86","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[17.50*c, >= , 1500 , c , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Joni sells kitchen aprons online for $32.50 each. How many aprons must she sell next month if she wants to earn at least $1,000?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":3,"Answer":"x>=31","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[32.50*a, >= , 1000 , a , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Mona is planning her son's birthday party and has a budget of $285. The Fun Zone charges $19 per child. How many children can she have at the party and stay within her budget?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":3,"Answer":"x<=15","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":" [[19*c, <= , 285 , c , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Moshde runs a hairstyling business from her house. She charges $45 for a haircut and style. Her monthly expenses are $960. She wants to be able to put at least $1,200 per month into her savings account order to open her own salon. How many \"cut & styles\" must she do to save at least $1,200 per month?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":4,"Answer":"x>=48","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[45*c, >= , 1200 + 960 , c , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Katherine is a personal chef. She charges $115 per four-person meal. Her monthly expenses are $3,150. How many four-person meals must she sell in order to make a profit of at least $1,900?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":4,"Answer":"x>=44","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[115*m - 3150, >= , 1900 , m , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Jake's water bill is $24.80 per month plus $2.20 per ccf (hundred cubic feet) of water. What is the maximum number of ccf Jake can use if he wants his bill to be no more than $60?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":4,"Answer":"x<=16","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[24.80 + 2.20*c, <= , 60 , c , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"The elevator in Yehire's apartment building has a sign that says the maximum weight is 2100 pounds. If the average weight of one person is 150 pounds, how many people can safely ride the elevator?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":3,"Answer":"x<=14","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[150*p, <= , 2100 , p , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Five student government officers want to go to the state convention. It will cost them $110 for registration, $375 for transportation and food, and $42 per person for the hotel. There is $450 budgeted for the convention in the student government savings account. They can earn the rest of the money they need by having a car wash. If they charge $5 per car, how many cars must they wash in order to have enough money to pay for the trip?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":5,"Answer":"x>=49","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[5*c ,>=,110 + 375 + 42*5 - 450, c , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Eun-Kyung works as a tutor and earns $60 per hour. She has $792 in savings. She is planning an anniversary party for her parents. She would like to invite 40 guests. The party will cost her $1,520 for food and drinks and $150 for the photographer. She will also have a favor for each of the guests, and each favor will cost $7.50. How many hours must she tutor to have enough money for the party?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":5,"Answer":"x>=20","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[792 + 60*h, >= , 1520 + 150 + 40*7.50 , h , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Cesar is planning a four-day trip to visit his friend at a college in another state. It will cost him $198 for airfare, $56 for local transportation, and $45 per day for food. He has $189 in savings and can earn $35 for each lawn he mows. How many lawns must he mow to have enough money to pay for the trip?","Type":"Inequalities Equation","Level":5,"Answer":"x>=7","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[35*l ,>=, 198 + 56 + 45*4 - 189 , l , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
